Family, food and love. Life's three courses made easy.
Table Manners is a comedy, drama film directed by Leli Maki.
Housewife Megan's idyllic life is thrown into turmoil, when it emerges that her
husband, Lloyd, faces a heavy prison sentence for tax evasion.
Megan, caught completely unawares is sent into a tailspin as she, not only loses her husband, her home and her
comfortable suburban life, but also finds herself implicated in the tax fraud and facing jail time.
Down on her luck and with nothing to her name Megan
has to rediscover who she really is.
With the help of her son and her best friend, Lindiwe, she finds solace
and hope in her life-long love and affinity for cooking.
She learns that the path back home begins with realizing that she is
enough and all she needs is her family, food and love.
Life's 3 courses made easy.
Megan, played by Diaan Lawrenson.
Lindiwe, played by Renate Stuurman.
Lloyd, played by Neels Van Jaarsveld.
Kgotso, played by Thabo Malema.
Calculus, played by John Lata.
Annette, played by Fiona Ramsay.
Diana Cooper, Viscountess Norwich (née Lady Diana Olivia Winifred Maud Manners; 29 August 1892 – 16 June 1986) was an
English silent film actress and aristocrat who was a well-known social figure in London and Paris.
As a young woman, she moved in a celebrated group of intellectuals known as
the Coterie, most of whom were killed in the First World War.
She married one of the few survivors, Duff Cooper,
later British ambassador to France.
After his death, she wrote three volumes of memoirs which reveal
much about early 20th-century upper-class life.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.